Mss.B.H357.p
American Philosophical Society
- I. Correspondence
  - Imerto, Arthur D
  - Inches, James W
  - Indiana State Medical Association
  - Indiana University Bookstore
  - Indiana. State Board of Health
  - Indians Manufacturers Association
  - Industrial Association of Quincy, Inc.
  - Industrial Commentaries
  - Industrial Equipment News
  - Industrial Health
  - Industrial Health - Speeches
  - Industrial Health Conservancy Laboratories
  - Industrial Health Council
  - Industrial Hygiene
  - Industrial Hygiene Foundation of America, Inc.
  - Industrial Hygiene Foundation, Mellon Institute
  - Industrial Hygiene Organizations: Meetings
  - Industrial Medicine
  - Industrial Medicine Association
  - Industrial Nursing
  - Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc.
  - Infant Welfare Society
  - Information Bureau
  - Ingalls Shipbuilding Corporation
  - Ingersoll-Rand Co.
  - Ingle, Dwight J
  - Inland Container Corp.
  - Institute for Medical Research
  - Institute of Life Insurance
  - Institute of Living
  - Institute of Medicine of Chicago.
  - Institute of Organotherapy
  - Institute of Physical Medicine
  - Institute of Public Relations, Inc.
  - Inter-Hemisphere Trading Corp.
  - International Apple Association
  - International Association of Ice Cream Mfgrs.
  - International Center for Psychodietetics
  - International Health Board - Commission
  - International Journal of Leprosy
  - International Labour Office
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
  - International Oceanographic Foundation
  - International Salt Company, Inc.
  - International Yearbook and Statemen's Who' s Who
  - Interstate Aircraft and Engineering Corp.
  - Invitation to Learning
  - Iosselson, L E
  - Iowa. Department of Health
  - Irons, V Earl
  - Irving Trust Co., (NY)
  - Irving, Walter M
  - Irvington Varnish and Insulator Co.
  - Iseisch, Edward
  - Iseman, John E
  - Island Creek Coal Co.
  - Ismail, Mirza Muhammad
  - Israelson, E C
  - Italy - Minister of Finance
  - Ivory, Andrew R
  - Jack, Clyde A
  - Jack, Mrs. E W
  - Jackson County (MO) Medical Society
  - Jackson, H C
  - Jackson, Howard W
  - Jackson, Janet M
  - Jackson, Percy
  - Jacobs, Albert C
  - Jacobs, Ida M
  - Jacobs, John Hall
  - Jacobs, Louis
  - Jacobs, Philip P.
  - Jacobs, W P
  - Jaeger
  - Jaffe Agency, Inc.
  - Jaillite, Emree G
  - Jakubowsky, Joseph F J
  - Jambert, Ann
  - James Mfg. Co.
  - James, Harold R
  - James, Mrs. M
  - James, Virginia
  - Jameson, Sir William
  - Jameson, W W
  - Jamison, Mrs. F B
  - Janoff, Milton
  - Jaquin, R. F. Company
  - Jay Garment Co.
  - Jay Norris Corporation
  - Jean, Sally Lucas
  - Jeffards, Jean A
  - Jefferson Davis Hotel
  - Jefferson Medical College
  - Jefferson Medical College Alumni Association
  - Jegant, Emil
  - Jenkins Brothers
  - Jenkins, Alfred
  - Jennings, W N
  - Jensen, Frances
  - Jensen, Helen
  - Jesuit Seminary Fund Jesuit Philippine Bureau
  - Jewish Vocational Service
  - Jhengliu
  - Joffe, Mrs. Bella
  - Johansen, F A
  - Johmann, Pauline
  - John Crerar Library
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance, Co.
  - John Hopkins. School of hygiene and Public Health
  - John Marshall Hotel
  - John O'London Weekly
  - Johns Hopkins University
  - Johnson and Johnson
  - Johnson, Louise S
  - Johnson, Richard A
  - Johnson, Robert W
    See: Clinical Club, in:
  - Johnson, S H
  - Johnson, Wentworth P
  - Johnson,Alvin
  - Johnston, Marguerite
  - Johnston. Bruce
  - Johnstone, Rutherford T
  - Johnstone, Thomas J
  - Johnstown (Pa) Chamber of Commerce
  - Johnstown, Pa, Junior Chamber of Commerce
  - Johnstown, Pa, Mayor
  - Johnstown, Pa., Flood Materials
  - Jolly, G G
  - Jones, Alfred W: Fortune Memorandum on Medical Economics
  - Jones, C C
  - Jones, Carol Hughes
  - Jones, George W
  - Jones, Guy P
  - Jones, Harriet M
  - Jones, Helen B
  - Jones, Hylda Sue
  - Jones, Isaac H
  - Jones, John Page
  - Jones, John Price, Corp.
  - Jones, Judy
  - Jones, Leonard Carter
  - Jones, Mrs. Walter McKay
  - Jones, Thomas Jesse
  - Jones, Waldo
  - Jordan, Thomas G
  - Jost, Theodore A
  - Journal of Living
  - Joy, Mr
  - Joyce & Mattis
  - Juckett, Eunice T
  - Judson Health Center
  - Judson, Thomas M
  - Jules Coffee Company
  - Junker, Ralph Daniel
  - Kaas, Josephine
  - Kabalkin, Rose
  - Kaeslin, Thelma
  - Kahn, Herbert
  - Kahn, Robert
  - Kaiser, Marius
  - Kalamazoo Tuberculosis Association
  - Kales, Peter
  - Kalfatis, Mary
  - Kalkbrenner, Edward
  - Kamsler, Patricia Mary
  - Kan (India), (re Rockfeller Foundation Grant In India)
  - Kansas City (MO) Chamber of Commerce
  - Kapadia, A R
  - Kaplan, Harold
  - Kaplan, Oscar
  - Karn, Estella
  - Karr, D Arthur
  - Kastlin, George J
  - Katz, Aaron
  - Kaufman, Nathan
  - Kaufmann, Elvira F
  - Kaufmann, Ursula
  - Kaumagraph Company
  - Kayser, Mary
  - Kean, B H
  - Kean, Ben
  - Keasby & Mattison
  - Keating, Helen
  - Keating, William
  - Kee, Pauline Rung
  - Keen, William W
  - Keiran, Joseph P
  - Keiser and keiser, Inc.
  - Keller, Donald R
  - Keller, L A
  - Kellogg Co.
  - Kellogg Service
  - Kellogg, John Harvey
  - Kellogg, W K
  - Kelly, Alice Mckay
  - Kelly, Emerson Crosby
  - Kelly, R G
  - Kelso, W M
  - Keltie, Anna E
  - Kelynack, T N
  - Kemble, Mrs. E B
  - Kendall Mills
  - Kendall, Henry
  - Kendrick Mfg. Co.
  - Kendrick, J F
  - Kennedy, Robert Lawson
  - Kenney, John
  - Kenney, Michael
  - Ken-Rad Tube & Lamp Corp.
  - Kentucky Tuberculosis Association
  - Kentucky. Department of Health
  - Kenyon, Theda
  - Keppel, Frederick P
  - Kernahan, R H
  - Kernan, W E
  - Kerner, Beatrice M
  - Kerr, Mrs. William
  - Kerr, Thomas B
  - Kerr, W R
  - Keshner, Edythe
  - Kessler, Henry H
  - Keys, Clement Melville
  - Keyser, Norman
  - Keystone View Company
  - Kieffer, Paul
  - Kiehle, Frederick A
  - Kiely, & Mueller, Inc.
  - Kienast, Margate
  - Kieran, Joseph P
  - Kiernan, Edmund
  - Killian, Wayne T
  - Kilpatrick, William D
  - Kimmel, Oscar P
  - Kind, Marie
  - Kinde, Matthew R
  - King Features Syndicate Inc.
  - King, Barry G
  - King, Bertha
  - King, David W
  - King, E L
  - King, Grace W
  - King, LeRoy
  - King, Mary Eleanor
  - King, Mrs.
  - King, Mrs. Nell Lynn
  - King, W V
  - Kingdom, Arthur F
  - Kingsbury, A Neave
  - Kingston Cake Co.
  - Kinkaid, Carl
  - Kinsman, Willard Q
  - Kips Bay (NY) - Yorkville District Health Committee
  - Kirban, Salem
  - Kirby, Mary
  - Kirby-Smith, J L
  - Kirkbride, F B
  - Kise, Yoshiaki
  - Kisecker, P K
  - Kister, Oran L
  - Kita,Sue
  - Kitasato Institute
  - Kittermaster, Sir Harold B
  - Kittinger Furniture Co., Inc.
  - Kitzeran, Kathe
  - Kiwanis Club (NYC)
  - Klank, Loretta
  - Klann, Bertha
  - Kleckner, Martin S
  - Klein
  - Klein, Institute
  - Klein, Josef
  - Klein, Warren E
  - Kleinischmidt, Earl G
  - Kline, Dorothea R
  - Klingbiel, Floyd
  - Klingenstein, Mrs. Percy
  - Klipstein, Ursula
  - Knack, A V
  - Knerr, Harry O
  - Knipp, Carrie
  - Knopf, Alfred A, Inc.
  - Knopf, S Adolphus
  - Knott, Arthur D
  - Knowles, Evelyn Sherman
  - Knox, Mrs. C
  - Kobau, Margareta
  - Koch Refrigerators
  - Koehnle, MRS. B A
  - Koenig, Mrs. M H
  - Kohberg, Luisa
  - Koo, Frances
  - Koperberg, S
  - Kopp, Marie E
  - Koren, F
  - Korff, Serge A
  - Kortrecht, Mary Bee
  - Kosloff, S
  - Kraditor and Haber
  - Kraditor, Abraham
  - Kraditor, Mrs. Abraham
  - Kraft, Frances L
  - Kraft-Phenix Cheese Corporation
  - Krajewski, E H
  - Krasnow, Frances
  - Krath, John C., Inc.
  - Krausz, Charles E
  - Kremer, Helen Elwyn
  - Krieger, Irving
  - Krug Baking Co.
  - Krug, Oscar P
  - Krumbhaar, Edward B
  - Krusen, Elizabeth G
  - Kubu, Laura H K
  - Kuh, Clifford
  - Kuhn, Hedwig S
  - Kuhns, Dwight N
  - Kull, Lorenz
  - Kumagai, Ray and Chris
  - Kunkle, Charles, Jr.
  - Kuromiya, M
  - Kyak, Susan
  - Laakso, Jenny
  - Lacher, G H
  - Laddey, John V
  - LaGuardia, Fiorello H
  - Lake Placid Club
  - Lamb, Carl J
  - Lambert, Allen C
  - Lambert, Eloisa
  - Lambert, Sylvester M
  - Lampson, Robin
  - Landis, H R
  - Landry, Mrs. Robert J (Marcia)
  - Lane, Arnell
  - Lane, Bryant B
  - Lane, D R
  - Lange, Jer
  - Lankenau Hospital
  - Lankenau Hospital Research Institute
  - Lanza, A J
  - Lapham, Maxwell
  - LaPlant-Choate Mfg., Inc.
  - Lapointe Machine Tool Co.
  - Lara, Casimire B
  - Larcher, S F
  - Larkin, Pauline
  - Larsen, Nils P
  - Larson, Benedict
  - Larum, Magda
  - Laschinsky, Etna
  - Lasker, Albert D
  - Lasker, Mary (Mrs. Albert D. Lasker)
  - Lasker, Mary Woodward
  - Lasky, Betty
  - Lasley, John R
  - Latham, Lois
  - Latif, Ahmed Abdel
  - Lautz, Julius A
  - Lauy, Mary Lernand
  - Laves, Walter H C
  - Laviola, Anthony L
  - Law, A N A
  - Law, Richard E
  - Lawrence, Richard W
  - Leach, Charles N
  - Leach, Robert J
  - League for Political Education
  - League of American Writers
  - League of Classroom Teachers
  - Leake, E W
  - Leary, John A
  - Leavitt, Catherine
  - Leber, Charles T
  - LeClerc, J A
  - Ledger Syndicate
  - Ledoux & Co., Inc.
  - Lee Foundation for Nutritional Research
  - Lee, Alice
  - Lee, H R
  - Lee, Halfdan
  - Lee, Higginson & Co.
  - Lee, Stanley
  - Leet, Dorothy F
  - Leete, H S
  - Lefler, Winetta A
  - LeFurge, Dorothy J
  - Legge, Robert T
  - Lehman, L Graham
  - Leibo, Joseph S
  - Leidesdorf, Samuel D
  - Leigh, W Colston, Inc.
  - Leipen, Friedrick
  - LeJeune, Eugenia
  - Leland Hayward & Co., Ltd
  - Lelansky, Ross S
  - Lelli, Louise
  - Lemont, Arthur E
  - Lemphers, G D
  - Leon, J Valesquez de
  - Leonard Wood Foundation
    See: American Leprosy Foundation in
  - LePla, Mrs. Fannie M
  - LePrince, J A
  - Leprosy Association
  - Leprosy in Florida
  - Leprosy Literature
  - Leprosy
  - Leprosy: Leonard Wood Foundation
  - Leprosy: World Health Organization
  - Lesem, Jeanne
  - Leuba, M Arthur
  - Levenson, Beatrice
  - Levenson, Fanny
  - Lever Brothers Company.
  - Leverone, L E
  - Levet, Margaretta Smith
  - Levin, Anne C
  - Levine, Estelle
  - Levy, Albert H
  - Levy, Anne
  - Levy, Julius
  - Levy, Robert E. & Co.
  - Lewi, Maurice J
  - Lewis, Clarence Mc K
  - Lewis, Clark L Jr.
  - Lewis, Edith Greenough
  - Lewis, Elmer
  - Lewis, Frederick A
  - Lewis, Mary
  - Lewis, Sir Wilmott
  - Lewyt Corp.
  - Lewyt Metal Products Co.
  - Leyendecker, R. R., Inc.
  - Libby Owens Ford Glass Co.
  - Liberty Lace and Netting Works
  - Liberty Mutual Insurance Company
  - Lichtwardt, Hartman A.
  - Lida Bonfield Employment Agency
  - Lieth, Frieda M Von Der
  - Life Magazine
  - Lilco
  - Lilly - Tulip Cup Corp.
  - Lilly Research Laboratories
  - Lim, Ariston Bautista
  - Lin (Director of Health, Nanking)
  - Lincoln Electric Co.
  - Lindholm, A W
  - Lindsay, Dorothy
  - Lindsay, Emma Wise
  - Lindsey, Hugh M
  - Lindsey, Marion
  - Lippincott, J. B., Company.
  - Lipschitz, Kurt M
  - Lissauer, Herman
  - Lister Bros., Inc.
  - Liston, Edward F
  - Litchfield (Conn.) Historical Society
  - Litchfield Assessors
  - Litchfield County National Bank
  - Literary Clipping Service
  - Little, Brown and Company
  - Little, Ruth F
  - Liu, J Heng
  - Liveright, Otto K
  - Living War and Peace Memorial for the Borough of Manhattan
  - Livingood, John E
  - Livingston, Louis
  - Livingston, MRS. Harris
  - Livingston, William
  - Livingway, Clark
  - Llanos, F Ruiz
  - Llewellyn Biological Institute
  - Lloyd, S H
  - Lobo,G
  - Locke, L W
  - Lockheed Aircraft Corporation
  - Loeb, H
  - Loewe, Rudolf
  - Loewenberg, Peter-Christian
  - Loewenstein, Alice
  - Loewenstein, Ernst
  - Lohse, C P
  - Lomako, Theodore
  - London, Irving
  - Long, Charles-Francis
  - Long, Esmond R
  - Long, John D
  - Long, MRS.
  - Long, Mrs. Clayton L
  - Long, W K
  - Long,J D
  - Longcope, Warfield T
  - Longo, Vincent
  - Longworth, Duncan E
  - Looby, W E
  - Look.
  - Loomis, Helen
  - Loomis, M R
  - Loram, Charles T
  - Lorentzen, H. K., Inc.
  - Los Angeles Athletic Club
  - Los Angeles Breakfast Club
  - Los Angeles Day Care Committee
  - Loud, William T
  - Loughran, Mrs. John J (June Lockhart)
  - Louisana. Department of Health
  - Lovas, A J Jr.
  - Love, Mrs. H
  - Low, Mary Eleanor King
  - Lowe, W G S
  - Lowell Institute Cooperative Broadcasting Council
  - Lowenstein, Anna
  - Lowery, Margaret L
  - Lowman, J B
  - Lownes, John B
  - Lowry, Paul H
  - Lowry, R J
  - Lubinski, Maria
  - Luca, Ruby De
  - Luck, H F
  - Luckman, Charles
  - Ludlam. Clarence
  - Ludwick, Kathleen G Douglas
  - Ludwig, George D
  - Ludy, John B
  - Luke, Mrs. J W
  - Luken, O H
  - Lukens Steel Co.
  - Lundberg, Fred
  - Lunt, Storer B
  - Luongo, E P
  - Lutz, Bertha
  - Lyle, Gerard
  - Lynch
  - Lynch, Florrie Oliver
  - Lyndeman, Betty S
  - Lyons, Eugene
  - Lyons, William P
  - Lytle, Clyde F
  - MacCallum William George
  - MacDonald, Arthur R
  - MacDonald, D S
  - MacDonald, E L
  - MacDonald, Keith A
  - MacGregor, Robert Menzies
  - Machinery Builders, Inc.
  - Machlett Laboratories, Inc.
  - MacIlvaine, Anne
  - Mackall, Leonard L
  - MacKenzie, Ellen
  - MacKenzie, Virginia
  - Mackie, Thomas T
  - MacKintosh, Helen K
  - MacKintosh, Sarah May
  - MacLennon, W G
  - MacLeod, Emily C
  - Maclin, Charles L
  - Macnamara, Jean
  - MacNaught, George K
  - Macon, Laura W
  - MacPhedran, F Maurice
  - Macy, R H & Co.
  - Madden, John F
  - Madden's Transfer & Storage
  - Mademoiselle
  - Madison Foods
  - Maffey, J L
  - Magan, Percy T
    See: Coffey-Humber Treatment, in:
  - Magnet Mills, Inc.
  - Magruder, Mrs. O N
  - Mahaffey, J Lynn
  - Mahmoud Soliman & Son
  - Mahony, Walter M
  - Maine. State Bureau of Health
  - Mainzer, F
  - Malewicz, Helena Maria
  - Malewicz, Witold
  - Malpass, George U
  - Manager Convention Bureau
  - Manasse, M M
  - Mandelstam, Abraham
  - Manfred, Ernest Fred
  - Manhattan House
  - Manhattan Storage and Warehouse Co.
  - Manhattan Theater Ticket Service
  - Manila. Collector of Internal Revenue
  - Manille Manufacturing Corp.
  - Manire, P H
  - Mann, Elizabeth
  - Mann, Percy G
  - Mannhardt, L Alfred
  - Manny, J W
  - Manrique, Aurelio, Jr.
  - Manson, G
  - Manson-Bahr, Sir Philip
  - Manufacturers Association of Connecticut, Inc.
  - Manufacturers Association of Poughkeepsie
  - Manufacturers Association of Racine, Wisconsin
  - Manufacturers Association of Syracuse
  - Manufacturers Association of the City of Bridgeport, Conn., Inc.
  - Mar, C J
  - Marail, Mrs. H J
  - Marble, Alice
  - Marcus, Sidney
  - Marion, J C
  - Markell, Eleanor
  - Marks, Robert G
  - Marloth, Kurt
  - Marquis Who's who
  - Marquis, A N, Company.
  - Marrin, Oswald W
  - Mars and Harwell
  - Marshall, Florence E
  - Marshall, George C
  - Marshall, George C, Research Foundation
  - Marshall, R L
  - Marthens, Mary E
  - Martin, Andrew Paton
  - Martin, Donald S
    See: Journal of Experimental Medicine, in:
  - Martin, Edward E I
  - Martin, Ethel
  - Martin, F O
  - Martin, Francis C
  - Martin, Gustav J
  - Martin,Mrs. Florence
  - Martinez, Ethel
  - Martin-Parry Co.
  - Martz, Edward E
  - Masada. Youth Zionist Organization of America
  - Mason, Genevieve W
  - Mason, Max
    See: Rockefeller Foundation, in:
  - Massachusetts Safety Council
  - Massachusetts.Department of Labor and Industries
  - Maté, Rudolf
  - Materassi, Vanna
  - Mathews, Joseph F
  - Matlack, T Milton
  - Matthews, Mary A
  - Mattiazzo Bros.
  - Mattison, Berwyn F
  - Matzke, Mrs. Emil, Jr.
  - Maxcy, Kenneth F
  - Maxwell, James
  - Maxwell, William S
  - May, Herbert
  - Mayer, Frederick
  - Mayo, Katherine
  - Mayorga, Angela
  - Mayr, Franz X
  - Mayr, Olga
  - Mazer, S
  - McAnallen, Patricia A
  - McBride,Robert
  - McCabe, John, & Company
  - McCallister, Mrs. L O
  - McCann, John
  - McCarrison, Lady
  - McCarrison, Sir Robert
  - McCarthy, Ruth
  - McCaskey, Donald
  - McChesney, Frances
  - McClatchy, V S
  - McClelland, N C
  - McClure, H S
  - McClure, Mrs. Charles F W
  - McClure, Roy D
  - McCollum, E V
  - McConnell, Gertrude Allen
  - McConnell, W J
  - McCord Radiator & Mfg. Co.
  - McCord, Carey
    A Blind Hog's acorns (Book Review)
  - McCormick, Katharine Dexler (Mrs. Stanley)
  - McCoy, Frances (Mrs. Frank)
  - McCoy, Frank R
  - McCoy, George W
  - McCready, Louis D
  - McCready, Margaret
  - McCreary, E A
  - McCullough, David G
  - McCutcheon, W L
  - McDermott, Vincent T
  - McDonald, Robert F
  - McDowell, Samuel I
  - McEvoy, James
  - McEwen, A
  - McFadden Publications
  - McFarland, Joseph
  - McFarland, Ross A
  - McFetridge, Laura
  - McGee, Mrs. T E
  - McGill, Alexander
  - McGilliam, Eugene F
  - McGilliamn, Anita Dorothy
  - McGinnis, Mrs. Murray Gardner
  - McGow, W Jackson
  - McGraw-Hill Book Co.
  - McGrew, Jane Cooper
  - McGrew, Milton L
  - McGuiness, Larry J
  - McGuiness, Madge C L
  - McGusty, V W T
  - McIlvaine, J S
  - McIntosh, W A
  - McIntyre
  - McKean, James W
  - McKee, Carl E
  - McKeever, Christine
  - McKey, Electa
  - McKinley, Earl B
  - McKinley, Mrs. Earl B
  - McKinney, T N
  - McLaughlin, John J
  - McLaughry, Elizabeth
  - Mclay, Sybell E
  - McLean, Mattie
  - McLean, Ross H
  - McLeod, B F
  - McLeod, Florence Alden
  - McLeod, Mrs. Malcolm
  - McMahan, Joyce
  - McMillan, James G
  - McMillan, W T
  - McMillan, William
  - McMullen, R H
  - McNair, Harvey, Jr.
  - McNeil Machine & Engineering Co.
  - McNutt, Paul V
  - Mead Johnson & Co.
  - Meade, Julian R
  - Mealpack Corporation of America
  - Meals, R W
  - Meanes, J W
  - Mearns, W A
  - Medical Advisory Committee
  - Medical Aid to Russia
  - Medical and Professional Club, Inc.
  - Medical College of Virginia.
  - Medical Economics
  - Medical Record
  - Medical Service Bureau
  - Medical Society of Jefferson County, NY
  - Medical Society of Milwaukee County
  - Medical Society of the County of New York
  - Medical Society of the County of Westchester, Inc.
  - Medical Society of the State of Pennsylvania
  - Medical World Publishing Company, Inc.
  - Meehan, Jean
  - Meek, Ethel Rose
  - Megaw, J
  - Megias, José
  - Meharry Medical College
  - Meier, Dorothy N
  - Meigs, J. Aitken, Medical Association
  - Meiss, Kate D
  - Melcher, Frederic G
  - Melcher, John S
  - Meleney, Henry E
  - Meloney, Marie Mattingly
  - Memorial Hospital
  - Memphis (Tenn.) and Shelby Co. Health Department
  - Menasha Products Co.
  - Mendelsohn, Max
  - Mercado, Rosemary Cady
  - Merchant, E B
  - Merchant, Edward B Jr.
  - Mercier, Lucien H
  - Merck and Company, Inc.
  - Meredith, Emily E
  - Mergo, John
  - Merl, L F
  - Merlis, Ethel P
  - Merman, Solange
  - Merrill, E D
  - Merrill, Laura R
  - Merritt, Hubert B
  - Mersand, Joseph
  - Meserole, Walter M
  - Metcalf, William S
  - Metcalfe, A J
  - Methodist Episcopal Hospital, Ft. Wayne, Indiana
  - Metropolitan Club
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance Company
  - Metropolitan Opera Association
  - Meyer, Carl
  - Meyer, K F
  - Meyer, Marianne
  - Meyercord, Grace E
  - Michaelyan, H, Inc.
  - Michaud, Gustave
  - Michel, Marie
  - Michelson, Julius
  - Michelson, Violet
  - Michigan Central Terminal
  - Michigan Tuberculosis Association
  - Michigan, University of. Lecture Series
  - Middleweek, F F
  - Mierisch, Helene
  - Milbank Memorial Fund
  - Military -Naval Club
  - Milk
  - Milk Plant Monthly
  - Millard, Thomas F
  - Miller, A Donald
  - Miller, Beulah
  - Miller, Charles A
  - Miller, Clement S
  - Miller, Eleanor
  - Miller, Elliot
  - Miller, Fred D
  - Miller, H C
  - Miller, H R
  - Miller, Leo E
  - Miller, M M
  - Miller, Rowella
  - Miller, T Grier
  - Miller, Theodore H
  - Millhoff,C B
  - Milligan, MRS. Harold V
  - Mills, C A
  - Mills, Ellen K
  - Mills, Ray
  - Mills, Tuncy
  - Milne, George H
  - Mine Safety Appliance Co.
  - Miner, Charles H
  - Minner and Barrett, Inc.
  - Minno, Helen (Mrs. George)
  - Mississippi State Board of Health
  - Mississippi Valley Trust Co.
  - Missouri State Health Department
  - Modern Hospital Publishing Co., Inc.
  - Modern Industry
  - Modern Medicine
  - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Moister, George
  - Molina, Mme. Rene
  - Moll,A A
  - Molloy, Joseph M
  - Molnar, Paul
  - Molyneux, T Stuart
  - Monaci, Piero
  - Monday Evening Dining Club
  - Mongan, Carrie (Mrs. Charles)
  - Mongan, Margaret E
  - Monk, Howard H. and Assoc.
  - Mono Service Co.
  - Monsanto Chemical Company
  - Montague, Joseph F
  - Montefiore Hospital (NYC)
  - Montero, Aniceto
  - Montgomery Ward & Company
  - Montgomery, Charlotte E W
  - Montsanto Chemical Co.
  - Mooney, J J
  - Moore Corp., Ltd.
  - Moore Fabric Co.
  - Moore, Charles H
  - Moore, David D
  - Moore, Edward F
  - Moore, Elizabeth P
  - Moore, Geraldine G
  - Moore, MacEnnis
  - Morales, F E
  - Morantte, P C
  - Moreira, Joad G
  - Morely, Frances
  - Morgan Construction Co.
  - Morgan, C Stuart
  - Morgan, G P
  - Morgan, Marion Burt
  - Morison, J
  - Moro Educational Foundation
  - Morrill, George H., Co.
  - Morris & McVeigh
  - Morris Machine Works
  - Morris, Emory W
  - Morris, Rex, Jr.
  - Morrissey, W P
  - Morron, John R
  - Morrow, Joseph R
  - Morrow, William & Co., Inc.
  - Morse, Minna W
  - Mortell, J. W. Co.
  - Morton, Paul
  - Morton, Rosalie S
  - Moser, Ann
  - Moses, H E
  - Mosher, Gouverneur Frank
  - Moskowitz, Harry
  - Motion Picture Producers & Distributors of America, Inc.
  - Motor Car Owners
  - Mott, Madeline Neigel
  - Moulton, Forest Ray
  - Mount Vernon (NY) Department of Health
  - Mount Vernon Die Casting Corp.
  - Mountain Valley Water Co.
  - Mueller, Emma Wiegand
  - Mueller, Eric H
  - Mueller, Jo
  - Mueller, Meta F
  - Muenks, C Mabel
  - Muldoon, James M
  - Mulford, Grendon, R
  - Mulvihill, Ann
  - Mundt, Bernice W
  - Municipal Tuberculosis Sanitarium, Chicago, Ill.
  - Munroe, Vernon
  - Munson, E L
  - Münsterberg, Selma
  - Murphy Varnish Co.
  - Murphy, Cyrus W
  - Murphy, Frank
  - Murray, George S
  - Murray, Geraldine
  - Murray, John Watts
  - Murray,Y
  - Museum of Science and Industry
  - Museum Studio 26
  - Music in Industry
  - Musto, David F
  - Mutual Life Insurance Co. of NY
  - My Country Society
  - Myers, Dennis
  - Myers, Mary H
  - Myrin Institute, Inc.
  - Nagle, Patrick S
  - Nance, Fuller
  - Napoli, Fernando di
  - Nassau County (NY) Department of Health
  - Natesh
  - Nathan Mfg. Co.
  - National Arts Club
  - National Association for Practical Nurse Education
  - National Association of Book Publishers
  - National Association of Manufacturers
  - National Association to Control Epilepsy, Inc.
  - National Audubon Society
  - National Automatic Tool Co., Inc.
  - National Bibliophile Service
  - National Child Labor Committee
  - National City Bank of New York
  - National City Bank of New York, Manila
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene
  - National Committee on Films for Safety
  - National Confectioners' Association of the U.S., Inc.
  - National Conference of Bar Examiners
  - National Conservation Bureau
  - National Council of Jewish Women
  - National Council of the Episcopal Church
  - National Council on Rehabilitation
  - National Dairy Council
  - National Film Board - Canada.
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Inc.
  - National Fund for Medical Education
  - National Fund for Medical Education, Columbia University
  - National Health Assembly.
  - National Health Council
  - National Health Education Committee, Inc.
  - National Health Library
  - National Industrial Conference Board
  - National Industrial Information Committee
  - National Institutes of Health.
  - National League of American Pen Women
  - National Live Stock and Meat Board
  - National Metal-Art Mfg. Co.
  - National Motion Pictures Co.
  - National Noise Abatement Council
  - National Nursing Council, Inc.
  - National Oil Products Company
  - National Organization for Public Health Nursing
  - National Radiator Corp.
  - National Recreation Association
  - National Research Council
  - National Resources Planning Board
  - National Safety Council